export const defaultState = [
  {
    id: 'yskqx55q',
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'k6qtv9fn',
    title: 'Javascript',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      },
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: '8uc6bpfq',
    title: 'Redux',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: '5pi2319d',
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: '8220ftbc',
    title: 'Udacity',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'ci7mqpbe',
    title: 'CSS',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: '18ao9pv2',
    title: 'Ajax',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'Ajax meaning',
        answer: 'Ajax (Asynchronous JavaScript And XML)'
      },
      {
        question: 'AJAX has become very commonly used because',
        answer: 'It allows page content to be updated without requiring a full page reload.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Which statement about XML is false?',
        answer: 'Every XML document must have a DOCTYPE tag'
      },
      {
        question: 'The jQuery AJAX methods all require which parameter to be supplied?',
        answer: 'url'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'm1pjots3',
    title: 'Python',
    questions: [],
  },
  {
    id: 'e38zm81y',
    title: 'PHP',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'sojq71ko',
    title: 'Node',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'njfria8o',
    title: 'React Native',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'j0grzjrn',
    title: 'Java',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: '8tqhcaed',
    title: 'HTML',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    id: 'xh1ivbe5',
    title: 'React',
    questions: [
      {
        question: 'What is React?',
        answer: 'A library for managing user interfaces'
      },
      {
        question: 'Where do you make Ajax requests in React?',
        answer: 'The componentDidMount lifecycle event'
      }
    ]
  },
]



/*
 case ADD_CARD:
 return {
 ...state,
 decks: {
 ...state.decks,
 [action.deck]: {
 ...state.decks[action.deck],
 questions: [
 ...state.decks[action.deck].questions, ...action.card //i.e. {question: '?', answer: '!'}
 ]
 }
 }
 }


*
* */